<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Football Transfer Talk</title>
    <link>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/index.php</link>
    <description>The latest transfer news from the world of football</description>
    <item>
      <title>Neymar confirms he will make the switch from PSG to Manchester United in the summer.</title>
      <link>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=104</link>
      <guid>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=104</guid>
      <description>In a surprising announcement Neymar confirmed he will be playing his football in the red of Manchester next season. "I am eager to begin my life in Manchester, it has been a dream of mine to play under the old Trafford lights since I was a young kid" -Neymar confirmed to Football Transfer Talk. There is no question the former Barcelona player will improve the squad depth of Manchester United but with Jese Lingard scoring one goal this season, he will have to fight for his spot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yaya Toure leaves Olympiakos after just three months and five games for Greek club</title>
      <link>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=103</link>
      <guid>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=103</guid>
      <description>The 35-year-old midfielder left Manchester City in the summer after his contract expired, and went on to rejoin Olympiakos in September.  The move signalled a return to the Greek Super League club Toure initially made his mark in Europe with 12 years ago.  However, at the time of signing the club did not release financial details or information of the contract's duration, and the Ivorian's second stint at Olympiakos has ultimately ended after just five appearances, with two coming in the league.  A statement on the club's website said: "Yaya is and remains an important member of the Olympiakos family, who has marked a central part of the history of the club. Olympiakos would like to thank him for everything he has offered to the club.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Gomez extends Liverpool contract until 2024</title>
      <link>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=102</link>
      <guid>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=102</guid>
      <description>Gomez has made 59 appearances for the current Premier League leaders since joining from Charlton for £3.5m in 2015 and earned six England caps. "Signing this new deal means the world to me," he told Liverpool's website. "I've been at the club a few years now and have had the pleasure to play for Liverpool and experience what that means, so I am delighted to get the chance to extend my contract here. "I love the club, I love playing and learning here, and I am happy for that to continue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chelsea intend to convince Eden Hazard to stay and sign new contract</title>
      <link>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=20</link>
      <guid>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=20</guid>
      <description>The 27-year-old has two years left on his current deal and the west London club are hopeful of agreeing new terms.  The Belgium star is in some of the best form of his career under Maurizio Sarri, and the Blues went joint-top of the Premier League at the weekend.  Chelsea were in talks with Hazard over a new deal last season but those discussions were put on hold amid interest from Real Madrid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marcos Alonso reveals he is set to sign Chelsea extension</title>
      <link>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=19</link>
      <guid>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=19</guid>
      <description>The left-back has been a key figure as Chelsea have started the season brightly under Maurizio Sarri.  He is under contract until 2021, but has told Spanish newspaper AS that he has been offered an extension by Chelsea.  "I am very calm and very happy at Chelsea, and the club must also be happy with me because, although I still have two years left on my contract, they have offered me an extension.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jadon Sancho signs new Borussia Dortmund contract</title>
      <link>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=18</link>
      <guid>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=18</guid>
      <description>The 18-year-old joined Dortmund from Manchester City last summer, and went on to make 12 Bundesliga appearances last season - scoring once and recording four assists.  A bright start to the 2018-19 season, which sees Sancho top the assists table with five after six league games, has led to a new four-year extension at the club.  "I am very glad that I decided to move to Dortmund just over a year ago, because everything turned out to be true: this city lives football like no other, and at BVB young players are given playing time," Sancho told the club's website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Euro Paper Talk: Chelsea given boost in bid to sign Barcelona midfielder Ivan Rakitic</title>
      <link>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=17</link>
      <guid>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=17</guid>
      <description>Barcelona midfielder Ivan Rakitic will not be handed the new contract he desires, with club president Josep Maria Bartomeu telling him to wait until next season. The Croatian's current deal runs until 2021 but after interest from other clubs this summer he stated that he would stay put and sign a new contract at Barcelona. The latest developments could alert those clubs who were looking to sign the 30-year-old midfielder, which included Paris Saint-Germain and Chelsea. (Onda Cero)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Euro Paper Talk: Doubts over Mauro Icardi's future at Inter Milan</title>
      <link>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=16</link>
      <guid>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=16</guid>
      <description>Contract talks between Mauro Icardi and Internazionale have stalled over the striker's salary demands. Inter thought they had reached an agreement to pay the 25-year-old €6.5m a year, but the Argentine's representatives are now requesting €8m. The club are keen to get Icardi tied down to a new contract and raise his €110m release clause to €130m. (Corriere della Serra)&#13;
&#13;
Juventus have edged to the front of the queue to sign Cagliari midfielder Nicolo Barella in 2019. Barella, 21, who has been capped for Italy at every level from U15 up to U21 scored six goals in 34 Serie A matches last season and was pursued throughout the summer by Inter and Milan, although neither was able to match Calgiari's €35m valuation. Ligue 1 side Monaco are also interested but Juve may already have a verbal agreement with Barella as the Bianconeri are the best route for him getting into the full Italy squad. (Calciomercato)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Euro Paper Talk: Barcelona want Adrien Rabiot transfer in January</title>
      <link>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=15</link>
      <guid>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=15</guid>
      <description>Paris-Saint Germain star Adrien Rabiot remains a Barcelona transfer target and the La Liga champions may attempt to bring him to the Camp Nou in January. The midfielder is out of contract next summer and that may mean he is available at a knockdown price when the transfer window reopens. (Sport)&#13;
&#13;
Atletico Madrid's Antoine Griezmann feels he has now reached the same level as Cristiano Ronaldo and Leo Messi. "I believe so. I know other players are emerging and I am conscious that I can improve my game too, yet this is a driving force for me, improve, win more and keep winning by playing in the manner we play." (AS)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harry Maguire has no buy-out clause in new Leicester City contract</title>
      <link>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=14</link>
      <guid>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=14</guid>
      <description>It means any future bids for the England defender can be rejected the Foxes should they maintain their stance of not wanting to sell him.&#13;
&#13;
Maguire signed a five-year deal earlier this month following a summer of transfer speculation where Manchester United were unsuccessful with two bids for the 25-year-old, the biggest of those understood to be worth £60m.&#13;
&#13;
Negotiations over an improved contract began when Maguire returned from the World Cup, with Leicester keen to reward the man described by manager Claude Puel as the "club's best player". Maguire played every minute for Leicester in last season's Premier League as they finished ninth, and featured in all seven of England's World Cup games as they reached the World Cup semi-finals.&#13;
&#13;
He has also been an ever-present for the Foxes in the league this campaign, picking up his third yellow card in five games during last Saturday's loss at Bournemouth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raheem Sterling and Manchester City set for fresh contract talks</title>
      <link>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=13</link>
      <guid>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=13</guid>
      <description>Sky Sports News understands that reports of an impasse in discussions are inaccurate and that City's director of football, Txiki Begiristain will hold talks with Sterling's representatives before the end of September.&#13;
&#13;
Sterling is out of contract in June 2020 and City have no option to extend his stay at the Etihad for another 12 months.&#13;
&#13;
On Friday, City manager Pep Guardiola told reporters: "It's well known we're delighted with him and would like him to continue. My club knows my opinion and we share that. After that it is the club and the agent." Sterling signed for the current Premier League champions in 2015 from Liverpool and has since made 144 appearances in all competitions, scoring 47 goals.&#13;
&#13;
He was also a key member of Gareth Southgate's England squad who made it to the World Cup semi-final in Russia this summer.&#13;
&#13;
Sterling has three Premier League goals so far this season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Tavernier extends Rangers stay until 2022</title>
      <link>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=12</link>
      <guid>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=12</guid>
      <description>The 26-year-old English defender moved to Rangers in July 2015 on a free transfer from Wigan.&#13;
&#13;
"I am delighted to go through the window and still be a Rangers player, and I have obviously been rewarded with a new contract," Tavernier said.&#13;
&#13;
"So I am absolutely buzzing with that and it is thanks to the club and my representatives for pulling it over the line. "I've always seen this as the place for me to play football. Rangers have always been great for me for giving me the foundation to start playing again and to start my career over again, and I will always hold that closely.&#13;
&#13;
"There was a bit of interest in the summer, but I was fully focused on working with the gaffer in this new campaign being captain as well."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manchester United's David de Gea says it is good for him to be a part of the club</title>
      <link>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=11</link>
      <guid>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=11</guid>
      <description>The Spain international has entered the last year of his current deal at Old Trafford - although the club can then opt to trigger a one-year extension.&#13;
&#13;
But United will be hoping to have agreed a new long-term extension with their four-time player of the year before then, and he offered some encouragement ahead of Wednesday's Champions League opener. &#13;
Manchester United goalkeeper David de Gea says he is "really happy" at the club, as talk continues about him possibly signing a new long-term contract.&#13;
their four-time player of the year before then, and he offered some encouragement ahead of Wednesday's Champions League opener.&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
00:4203:31&#13;
Asked if he was considering signing a contract, De Gea said: "I feel really loved at this club. From the fans, from all the people who are for this club.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethan Ampadu signs five-year Chelsea contract extension</title>
      <link>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=10</link>
      <guid>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=10</guid>
      <description>The 18-year-old Wales international is yet to feature under new head coach Maurizio Sarri, but made seven appearances under his predecessor Antonio Conte last term.&#13;
&#13;
Warnock keen on Ampadu loan&#13;
&#13;
Speaking to Chelsea's official club website, he said: "I'm really proud and happy. I'm looking forward to the next five years and all I have got to do now is continue to work hard, and hopefully good things will happen."&#13;
&#13;
Chelsea director Marina Granovskaia added: "Ethan has shown great potential and unbelievable maturity since arriving at Chelsea a year ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Petr Cech unsure of Arsenal future</title>
      <link>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=9</link>
      <guid>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=9</guid>
      <description>Petr Cech admits he is playing for his future at Arsenal and says the goalkeeping situation is "complicated".&#13;
&#13;
The 36-year-old, who has started all Arsenal's Premier League games this season, has yet to be offered a contract extension with less than 12 months remaining on his current deal.&#13;
&#13;
The Gunners signed Bayer Leverkusen 'keeper Bernd Leno for £19.2m in the summer and Cech accepts competition for places is stiff.&#13;
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ross McCormack joins Central Coast Mariners on season-long loan</title>
      <link>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=8</link>
      <guid>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=8</guid>
      <description>Aston Villa forward Ross McCormack has joined Australian side Central Coast Mariners on a season-long loan.&#13;
&#13;
The move could see the 32-year-old Scot link up with Usain Bolt, who is on trial with the Mariners as he pursues a career as a professional footballer.&#13;
&#13;
McCormack has experience of playing in the A-League from his time on loan at Melbourne City last season.&#13;
&#13;
The forward moved to Aston Villa in August 2016 from Fulham, but has failed to make an impact at Villa Park.&#13;
&#13;
He has just three goals in 24 matches for the club and last played for Steve Bruce's side in September 2017.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cristiano Ronaldo admits to anxiety before first Juventus goals</title>
      <link>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=7</link>
      <guid>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=7</guid>
      <description>Cristiano Ronaldo admitted there was "a bit of anxiety" following his move from Real Madrid to Juventus, where he finally opened his account on Sunday.&#13;
&#13;
The forward joined the Serie A champions for £105m this summer after calling time on his nine-year stay in Madrid.&#13;
&#13;
The 33-year-old failed to score in his opening three league games for Juventus - a goal drought by his own lofty standards - but he got up and running with a double in their 2-1 over Sassuolo.&#13;
&#13;
Victory helped Juve maintain their perfect start in Serie A, and while the match was marred by a Douglas Costa spitting incident, Ronaldo revealed his relief at rediscovering his goalscoring boots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Terry turns down Spartak Moscow move for family reasons</title>
      <link>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=6</link>
      <guid>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=6</guid>
      <description>Sky in Italy reported last week that the former England and Chelsea captain was in talks over a one-year deal, with the option of an extra 12 months.&#13;
&#13;
Terry - who has two children - underwent a medical in Rome last weekend, but has now decided against moving to Russia.&#13;
&#13;
In a statement on Instagram, he said: "After considerable thought, I have decided to decline a contract offer from Spartak Moscow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boateng says he rang Man Utd boss Jose Mourinho to explain reasons for rejecting move</title>
      <link>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=5</link>
      <guid>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=5</guid>
      <description>Sky sources reported last month the Bayern Munich centre-back spurned a potential move to Old Trafford as he did not feel Manchester United were serious contenders to win the Champions League.&#13;
&#13;
Boateng, who has spent the last seven seasons at Bayern, has now spoken publicly for the first time about Mourinho's interest in bringing him to United.&#13;
&#13;
"I had enquiries from Paris-Saint Germain and Manchester United, and I considered them," the former Manchester City defender told Bild.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European Paper Talk: Lucas Hernandez rejected Man Utd move</title>
      <link>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=4</link>
      <guid>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=4</guid>
      <description>Atletico Madrid defender Lucas Hernandez is a Manchester United transfer target and they may launch another move in January. France international Hernandez, 22, has established himself as a regular for club and country and signed a new contract with Atletico in the summer until 2024. United and Manchester City both tried to tempt the player during the first week of August, with United offering €80m (£71.17m) and planning to double his salary. He has no plans to leave but interest is still there. (Marca)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sami Khedira signs new three-year Juventus contract</title>
      <link>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=3</link>
      <guid>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=3</guid>
      <description>The Italian champions also have the option of extending the German international's deal by a further 12 months.&#13;
&#13;
Khedira tweeted: "Since my first day I've had a special feeling and it quickly felt like home here.&#13;
&#13;
"I'm very proud to be a part of the great history of the club and of the Juventus family. Let's continue to make black and white history."&#13;
&#13;
The 31-year-old joined Juventus from Real Madrid in 2015 and has won three Serie A titles during his time in Italy.&#13;
&#13;
Khedira also has 77 caps for Germany and was part of the squad that won the 2014 World Cup.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sir Alex Ferguson wanted Ilkay Gundogan to replace Paul Scholes at Manchester United</title>
      <link>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=2</link>
      <guid>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=2</guid>
      <description>Ilkay Gundogan was one of Sir Alex Ferguson's final targets before the Manchester United boss retired in 2013, according to the club's former coach Rene Meulensteen.&#13;
&#13;
Ferguson called time on his coaching career after steering United to a 13th Premier League title in the 2012-13 season.&#13;
&#13;
A memorable campaign saw Robin van Persie score 26 times, while it was also midfielder Paul Scholes' final year at Old Trafford after he was talked out of retirement by Ferguson in early 2012.&#13;
&#13;
Meulensteen - a first-teach coach under Ferguson at the time - admitted Gundogan, then of Borussia Dortmund, was wanted by the Scot as a replacement for Scholes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chelsea winger Willian wants five more years at Stamford Bridge</title>
      <link>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=1</link>
      <guid>https://mayar.abertay.ac.uk/~1604475/WebDev/View/Article.php?id=1</guid>
      <description>Willian insists he never wanted to leave Chelsea in the summer and hopes he will remain at Stamford Bridge for the next five years.&#13;
Manchester United were interested in signing Willian, while Barcelona had three bids turned down for the Brazil international.&#13;
Willian previously claimed there was "no chance" he would have stayed at Chelsea had Antonio Conte remained as manager, but now the 30-year-old insists he never considered leaving the club.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
